filmjunk.com 2019-09-13

# Privacy Policy for FilmJunk.com - Film Junk

Here at Film Junk, the privacy of our readers is extremely important to us.

We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Film Junk, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Contests**  
Any of the personal information collected for contests, giveaways or other promotions on Film Junk are never shared with anyone outside of our own staff and the companies sponsoring the promotion. The information is only used in order to provide the winners with the goods and/or services that they are entitled to as a result of the promotion.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This includes the ability to remember your login for posting comments, or for responding to surveys and reader polls.

**Advertisements**  
Film Junk uses third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, however, this could affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

For more information, you can reach us at [filmjunk at gmail.com](mailto:filmjunk@gmail.com) or visit the [Google Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).
